



PROFILE

As a UX/UI designer I'm always looking to explore and improve in my skills. I love being an advocate for others, especially when you can find solutions along the way. Creativity and flexibility drive my design process. Working with passionate people inspires me to do better! I come with a 10 year background in graphic design. This has brought a wonderful balance to my UX/UI career while delivering solutions for clients.

CONTACT

gothessmpls@gmail.com

PH. 971-344-4273

Minneapolis, MN

SKILLS | TOOLS

Paper & Pencil

Adobe XD

InVision

Figma

Google Drive

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Visual Studio Code

Code Pen

Trello

Mood board

Miro

CMS

Wordpress

Cargo

Bootstrap

HTML

CSS

Java

Github

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer & Marketing, Gothess, Minneapolis MN — 2017-Present

Gothess is small business for event planning in Minneapolis. As the graphic designer and event promoter, I focus on all concept designs, and event planning. The events have specific demographic that is strategically marketed. Creation of content for promotional use is directed for a various of platforms in social media, and at the events. Concept designs for each tailored event is my expertise, and all tasks are finalized through deadline to suit each planned event.

Graphic Designer, Gallery Mini, Portland OR - 2013-2016

Collaborating with gallery on design and marketing teams, on-site and remotely to design and/or update existing print and digital assets for the gallery. Design needs required digital branding, marketing collateral, press kits, gallery oversize signage and promotional flyers.

Graphic Designer & Marketing, Lake Oswego OR - 2012-2014

Designed digital and print collateral for a chain of grocery stores in Oregon. Coordinated production of materials with vendors, tracked jobs in progress, resolved any potential issues. Reviewed all marketing collateral within the departments to ensure the accurate implementation of each stores specific needs.

UX/UI CASE STUDIES

Civic Helper, UX/UI Designer, Minneapolis MN — 2021

The Civic Helper is a mobile app that makes it easy to discover, schedule and manage volunteer opportunities.

USDA Website Responsive, UX/UI Designer, Minneapolis MN - 2021

The goal for the USDA redesign was to make it responsive for desktops & mobile while improving the user experience flow in the navigation.

Community Pathways Responsive Redesign, UX/UI Designer, Minneapolis MN - 2021

Community Pathways wanted to implement a sign up form for their newsletter. The newsletter would be implemented in the primary navigation which includes a responsive redesign for both desktop & mobile.

EDUCATION

The School of Art Institute in Chicago(SAIC) — BFA, 2003

Website Link: https://gothessmpls.github.io/UX_19H_20HW/designprocess.html

Portfolio Link: https://www.instagram.com/mari_navarro_design/